# **Komal Dhawade**

komaldhawade4@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/komal-dhawade54455a222 | 9226607923, Pune

# **Summary**

A hardworking employee with customer service, multitasking, and time management abilities. Proven track record of on-time project delivery, with a focus on optimizing performance and enhancing user experience. Committed to staying current with industry trends.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Web Developer Intern**

Sep 2022 - Nov 2023

E6 Web Solutions | Pune, India

- Collaborated in the development of [ HTML, CSS, JavaScript, responsive design, angular] as part of a development team.
- Gained hands-on experience in [PHP, Git, PostgreSQL] through active participation in coding, testing, and debugging processes.
- Worked closely with team members to troubleshoot issues, optimize code, and improve application performance.
- Participated in daily stand-ups, code reviews, and knowledge-sharing sessions, fostering a collaborative and learning-oriented environment.

#### Junior Full Stack Java Developer-Intern

Feb 2022 – May 2022

MRND Lab Pvt.Ltd Internship | Pune, India

- Collaborated in the development of [specific features, modules, or projects] as part of a dynamic full-stack Java development team.
- Gained hands-on experience in [Java, Spring Boot, and MySQL] through active participation in coding, testing, and debugging processes.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Profit-Based Product Recommender System for Seller Zone (2022 - 06/2023)

This project focuses on utilizing MLP algorithms to find common patterns in transactional databases. **Java, Swing, Machine Learning, Databases, SMTP, Data Mining**.

#### Flight ticket booking platform (03/2022 - 05/2022)

Created a user-friendly Flight Ticket Booking Platform, streamlining the reservation process and enhancing the overall travel experience. Implemented features for flight search, booking, and payment processing using

[HTML, CSS, Angular js, java, spring boot and MySQL]. The project focused on providing a seamless and efficient interface for users to book and manage their flights.

## Book Management System Project (01/2022 - 02/2022)

Designed and implemented a streamlined Book Management System for efficient cataloging and tracking of library resources. Utilized [java, Spring-boot, MySQL, Angular] to enhance accessibility and optimize library operations.

# Sushiman-Frontend Website Project (01/2023-03/2023)

In this website we'll use following technologies: CSS variables, Import CSS files into other CSS files, Use flex and position properties in CSS, create smooth and subtle animations, Use the BEM naming method, maintain a well-organized file and folder structure, Embrace the principle of writing clean code.. [sushiman-frontend.netlify.app/], Utilizing[HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT].

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Advanced Program on Java Stack Development using Angular [July -2023, 381 Hrs.]

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Engineering (BE) – Information Technology 06/2022 - 07/2023, University of Pune, India

Diploma in Computer Engineering 06/2018 - 07/2020, Parikrama Polytechnic, Kashti, India

#### **SKILLS**

Java | Responsive Design | Backend Development | Git | AngularJS | MySQL | PostgreSQL | FRONT END | HTML5 | CSS | Bootstrap | JavaScript | PHP | Spring boot | Project Management | Communication | Leadership | Time Management | Adaptability | Problem Solving | Teamwork | Creativity